Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app
[dramatic music playing]
[hoofbeats]
[sudden hush]
[footsteps]
[high-pitched dive sound]
-[shrieks]
-[hisses]
[rattling]
[eagle shrieks]
[ghostly clattering]
[wailing cry]
[camel humming]
[man panting]
[man] Help.
[hoofbeats]
[grunts and pants]
Please.
[man] Help me.
[pants]
[gulping]
[gasps and pants]
[man] They are looking
for us.
[bandit] "Us"? All I see is
an old man in trouble.
[man] This is yours.
There's plenty of more gold.
In that cave.
Please.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[camel groans]
-[lumbering thumps]
-[camel grunting]
[man] Wait. Wait.
[grunts]
[pants]
-[grunts]
-[man] Hind. stop!
He's helping us.
-My daughter.
-[bandit] You are blessed.
[man] Wait.
Those are good mounts.
Not the mounts of bandits.
More like soldiers.
[bandit] Sassanid
by their armor.
So. tell me who you are.
-In time.
-[scoffs]
There's not much of that left.
The dagger is worth
ten pieces of gold.
I guarantee you ten more.
[scoffs] That shroud.
it has pockets?
I have gold.
Lakhmid gold.
Help us reach
the Shaybani settlement.
and it is yours.
The dagger and the gold.
You have my word.
[battle drum music playing]
[long groaning]
[lumbering thumps]
[hoofbeats]
[camel grunting]
[bandit] Into the dunes!
[horses neigh]
-[bell ringing]
-[camel groans]
[man] No. No!
Come on. Yalla!
[bandit] Other side
of the dune!
[bandit] Run!
Run!
-[rattling]
-[horses neigh]
[ominous music playing]
-[man 1] Got them!
-[man 2] Go. Go!
[bandit] Go.
Come on. Come on.
[battle drum music playing]
-[pants]
-[Hind pants]
[man 2] Mount up!
[horses neigh]
[Hind grunts]
[bandit] Go!
[battle drum music playing]
[horses neigh]
[dogs barking]
-[hollers]
-[bleating]
[children's sounds]
-[camels groan]
-[hoofbeats]
-[rattling]
-[chickens squawking]
-[crowd shouting]
-[horse neighs]
[Hind grunts]
[crowd shouting]
[man grunts]
Baba!
[children's sounds]
I come in peace... [grunts]
[grunts]
[Aasif] Kill him!
-[man] Wait! Wait.
-[crowd shouting]
[crowd chattering]
[Hani] What is this mischief?
[bandit pants]
Two vagabonds. brother.
Helped by this bandit.
And they bring mercenaries
to the border.
[crowd mumbling]
Let's see these vagabonds.
-[dogs barking]
-[crowd chattering]
[crowd chattering]
-[hoofbeats]
-[horse neighs]
[crowd mumbling]
-[doors opening]
-[sheep bleating]
[dramatic music playing]
[high-pitched dive sound]
Commander Jalabzeen.
[Hani] It's been a long time.
How can the Shaybani help you?
I'm here on the orders
of the Supreme Emperor Kisra.
ruler of your kingdom
and the lands
of the fertile crescent
where the Tigris
and the Euphrates
-flow into the sea.
-Something to drink?
[Jalabzeen] Your emperor
has sent me
to retrieve his subjects.
Al-Numan and Hind Bint Al-Numan.
That girl there.
His Highness. King Al-Numan
and Hind Bint Al-Numan.
Princess of Al Hira
are now guests in my home.
[crowd mumbling]
[Hani] You're also welcome
to our hospitality.
fresh horses if you need them
and safe passage home
as is my sworn
duty to my emperor.
[Jalabzeen exhales] Allow me
to enlighten you. Chief Hani.
That old man
is no longer a king.
as his appearance makes clear.
He is a fugitive. And Al Hira.
liberated from his rule.
is now governed by Ibn Qabisah.
a loyal subject of the emperor.
So. in the name
of Emperor Kisra.
I demand that
you hand over this girl.
who has been
made his concubine.
-[man 3] It is you
who is the emperor's whore!
-[gasps]
-[crowd shouting]
-[Jalabzeen grunts]
-Brother.
-Please.
-[Hind grunts]
-[Jalabzeen grunts]
-[crowd chattering]
-[gasps]
Please.
[man 4] She's a princess.
Leave her alone!
You won't stop running. huh?
-[Jalabzeen grunts]
-[crowd gasping]
-[Hind grunts]
-Samir!
[crowd shouting]
An emperor
who rules so many lands
is perhaps unaware
we. kings of the desert.
have never given our daughters
to others as tribute.
not even to pharaohs or caesars.
You may go in peace.
[pants]
[horse neighs]
Hyah!
[crowd chattering]
This isn't the first time
you've entered our land
without permission.
I will leave
as soon as I am paid.
[crowd mumbling]
Chief Hani. this man helped us.
I owe him.
Payment is his life.
Get lost. thief.
[soft music playing]
[long groaning]
[bell ringing]
-[sheep bleating]
-[children's sounds]
[indistinct talking]
[bandit] Hyah! Ha!
[crunchy sounds]
[exhales]
We could kill the father.
[sighs] The father
is not the problem.
Then we kill them all.
[dogs barking]
[children's sounds]
That would be a mistake.
[ominous music playing]
[sheep bleating]
We make it clear to them.
[indistinct talking]
[footsteps]
[grunts and exhales]
[indistinct talking]
-[hoofbeats]
-[horses neigh]
[hisses]
-[click]
-[inaudible]
Get in the water.
[hisses]
[shouting in foreign language]
[indistinct shouting]
[gasps and pants]
[Aasif] She's Lakhmid.
My daughter is Shaybani. Hani.
We ask Al-Numan
and his daughter to leave.
Two camels. Hani.
and we will leave
at first light.
No.
You are my guest.
That still means something
to the Shaybani.
While you're under my roof.
you and your daughter are safe.
And I won't cast them out.
[crowd mumbling]
[dramatic music playing]
[woman humming]
[humming]
[high-pitched dive sound]
[sheep bleating]
-[bell ringing]
-[sheep bleating]
[ominous music playing]
[screaming]
[indistinct talking]
[dramatic music playing]
-[screeching]
-[rattling]
[somber music playing]
[crunchy sounds]
[sizzling]
[high-pitched dive sound]
I need you to deliver
a message for me.
Do you hear me. boy?
Good.
Good boy.
My good. strong boy. huh?
[Jalabzeen] Huh?
Strong. strong man.
[sizzling]
[crickets rubbing]
[woman screaming]
[fire crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[somber music playing]
[bell ringing]
[indistinct shouting]
[woman 1] This girl has brought
the devil to our home.
-[bell ringing]
-[crowd wailing]
[woman 1] She is a curse on us.
[pants]
-[inhales and hums]
-[sizzling]
-[grunts]
-[bell ringing]
[tragic music playing]
[humming]
[thunder striking]
[dramatic music playing]
[sizzling]
-[Hind screams]
-[thump]
[falling sounds]
[camel groans and munches]
[Hind grunts]
[horse neighs]
[chuckles]
[pants]
[bandit] Looks like
my horse missed me.
Why are you still here?
Do you want something from me?
Huh?
Then pay me what you owe.
A dagger and gold.
[birds chirping]
Get out of here.
And leave my horse.
Have you no honor?
Honor is for fools
and princesses.
One slap from you is enough.
[Hind] I'm tired of fighting.
When trouble follows you.
you have no choice.
[thud]
[dramatic music playing]
Like I said. trouble.
[echoes] Hind Bint Al-Numan!
[crunchy sounds]
[grunts]
[echoes] How much?
Forty pieces of gold
should do it.
I told my father
not to trust you.
[horses grunting]
[Hind pants]
[echoes] You give her to him...
you go free.
Ugh.
[horse neighs]
[dramatic music playing]
Your life means nothing to you?
A deal with you
means nothing to me.
Make it to the horse
before they reach us.
[action music playing]
[Hind grunts]
[both grunting]
[battle drum music playing]
[grunts]
[Hind gasps]
-[water splashing]
-[grunts]
Argh.
[Hind grunts]
[fighting sounds]
[whistles]
[horses neigh]
To the horse!
[action music playing]
[grunts]
[battle drum music playing]
[grunting]
-[rattling]
-[grunting and screaming]
[horse neighs]
[all grunting and panting]
-[cracks]
-[grunting]
[continue grunting and panting]
-[bandit] Hind!
-[Hind grunts]
[bandit pants]
[Hind grunts]
-[horse neighs]
-Go.
[battle drum music playing]
-[grunting]
-[horses groaning]
[grunts]
-[horse neighs]
-Hyah!
[crowd shouting]
Ho! Ho! Ho!
[bandit grunts]
[crowd war chanting]
[Aasif] Let her go!
This is Shaybani land.
[crowd chattering]
Then Shaybani will pay.
-[bandit grunts]
-[crowd shouting]
Hey! Hey! To Ctesiphon!
Hyah! Hyah!
[buzzing]
[Samir] He saved her life.
Nine Sassanid killed
on our land.
[Samir] Kisra will punish us
for this.
The bandit is responsible.
[indistinct talking]
[indistinct shouting]
[Aasif] Who can't see that
we are at their mercy?
We are at their mercy.
What about honor. my brother?
Yes. and look what it got us.
There's bloodshed.
[indistinct shouting]
There's bloodshed!
Enough.
-[woman 2] Listen to me.
-Enough!
The bandit dies tomorrow.
[chicken clucking]
-[thud]
-Shh!
[chicken clucking]
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[sighs]
Things always get worse
when you show up.
-I brought you water.
-Do you care to pour?
Why didn't you give me over
to the Sassanid?
He is my enemy
just as much as he is yours.
[bandit] You are cutting
my skin.
I'm saving your life.
[bandit grunts]
[indistinct talking]
[Hind] So. where will you go?
[water chugging]
[bandit] The empty quarter.
With the other unwanted.
I owe you.
[bandit] That's right.
A dagger and gold.
Your life isn't enough?
[chokes and sighs]
I won't keep it long
without payment.
Then you better hope
to see me again.
May I never be so blessed.
[indistinct talking]
[singing]
[ominous music playing]
[Aasif] Go!
[Aasif] Go back.
Your insistence brought us here.
[Hani] We can't go back. Aasif.
What matters now is we stand by
Al-Numan and his daughter.
Guard and protect them.
Until when. Hani?
Until when?
[crowd chattering]
[Aasif] We're all dead?
-You let in outsiders. Lakhmids.
-[crowd chattering]
and pitted us. your tribe.
against an empire.
Your tribe. brother.
-For what?
-Aasif!
You expect us
to lay down our lives
for others not of our clan.
You act like an enemy
to your people.
-[crowd chattering]
-[grunts]
[man 5] What are you doing?
Dare you dishonor me?
Challenge me again. brother.
and it's you
who will be banished.
[Aasif chokes.
pants. and coughs]
Al-Numan and his daughter
will remain with us
as long as I am your leader.
[Hani] Is that understood?
Is that understood?
[dramatic music playing]
They are protecting their queen.
[Hind] Those ants will die.
[dog barking]
[crickets rubbing]
[scoffs]
-Apricots.
-Mhm.
-[chuckles]
Tastes like home.
[Al-Numan] Mhm.
I would like to sit in the grove
one more time.
We will never see Al Hira again.
When I'm gone.
you'll become
the rightful queen
of our people.
Until then.
Hani will protect you.
You protect me.
[Hind] We protect each other.
Always.
[soft music playing]
[door knocking]
-[door knocking]
-[Aasif] Open the door!
-You were seen.
-[man 6] Let us through.
-Let us through!
-[man 7] Move.
-Move!
-[crowd chattering]
[Aasif] Up. Look for him.
[man 6] Over here. Over there.
Look. Look.
[rattling]
Get out.
You were seen.
By who?
[Safiya] She was inside
all evening.
I was watching her.
You see?
Now get these men
out of my room.
-Keep looking.
-[man 6] Over there.
[indistinct shouting]
[indistinct talking]
It is for your own protection.
Why? My father protects me.
Your father is gone. Hind.
Gone?
Where has he gone?
[eventful music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[men shouting] Yeah!
[fighting sounds]
[crowd cheering]
-[crowd cheering]
-[Jalabzeen gasps]
[Jalabzeen pants and grunts]
[crowd cheering]
[both grunting]
-[weird laughing]
-[crowd cheering]
[crowd cheering]
[Vizier] Field Commander
Jalabzeen.
A mercenary who failed you
in his mission
to bring back
the desert concubine.
[Jalabzeen pants]
[Kisra] You fight with ferocity.
Commander Jalabzeen.
[dramatic music playing]
Yet you have been outmatched
by a desert girl.
[scoffs and sniffs]
Who are these Shaybani
that refuse me?
Why do they shelter the girl?
Honor.
[ominous music playing]
[women screaming]
[Kisra] Look up.
You may meet our eye.
And how might I honor you?
That I may go home.
And where is home?
On the shore
of the Black Sea. my lord.
[waves splashing]
I honor you
with one last opportunity
to bring me this man's daughter.
Then you may go home.
[crowd cheering]
[footsteps]
[sniffs and exhales]
[Kisra] You have traveled far.
Al-Numan Bin Al-Mundhir.
Though you came alone.
I offer you
something more valuable.
A king.
[crowd gasping]
[Kisra] You're no longer a king.
We replaced you
with Ibn Qabisah.
In prison.
you'll soon be forgotten.
Only one of us
will be forgotten.
[Al-Numan] Sparing my life
shows weakness.
You bait me.
[crowd shouting outside]
[crowd in unison] Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
There is no greater tragedy
than a man who gives up on life.
You have failed your people.
You have failed me.
[crowd in unison] Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
You will feel
your daughter's pain
throughout eternity.
[crowd cheering]
You cannot kill a king.
We will replace you.
[door opens]
[bang]
[Al-Numan pants]
[tense music playing]
[buzzing]
[thump]
Death comes for us all!
[women singing
in foreign language]
[Al-Numan pants]
[door opens]
[elephant roaring]
-[crowd cheering]
-[elephant trumpets]
[Al-Numan continues panting]
[Al-Numan] Let the lions
tear down your house!
[crowd cheering]
-[Al-Numan] Hind.
-[hushing]
[rumbling]
[singing sounds continue]
[somber music playing]
All I want now
is her Lakhmid head.
-Bring me that.
-[elephant groans]
[Vizier] Ibn Qabisah of Al Hira.
You will exterminate
every man. woman and child
in the Shaybani tribe
for the defiance.
Fail. Ibn Qabisah. and it is you
who will be called
onto the carpet.
[crowd shouting]
[Jester] There is only one thing
for a traitor.
Drag his body
through the streets of Ctesiphon
with a camel's cowl.
[crowd shouting]
[dark music playing]
[bird chirping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[splashing]
[crickets rubbing]
[fire crackling]
[dog barking]
[child's voice outside]
[Safiya] You should eat.
I don't need your advice.
Just more
of your sleeping draught.
Why did you lie for me?
I am an outsider. like you.
You're not Shaybani?
I am Ganim.
[Hind] You're Ganim?
Shaybani are my family now.
My family was my father.
The desert is home
with many rooms.
[scoffs]
It's time you become
who you might be.
[Hind] Help me dress.
[mysterious music playing]
[Hind] It's time for me
to return home. Hani.
I must help my people.
Your city is
under Kisra's occupation.
Better to die facing your enemy
than running from him.
[Hind] So. you will support me?
[soft tragic music playing]
[Hani] Your father was
as my father. Hind.
But my tribe is my family.
It's time I serve my tribe.
This is yours.
[soft tragic music continues]
[Hind] Then this burden
I will bear alone.
[ominous music playing]
[man 8] Sassanid!
Move out.
[thunder rumbling]
[dramatic music playing]
[man 8] Stand-by formation.
Forward.
[marching footsteps]
[sinister music playing]
[man 8 yelling order]
[screeching]
[marching footsteps]
[dramatic music playing]
-[hollers]
-[hoofbeats]
-Hyah! Hyah!
-[crowd talking]
[Hani] Hurry.
The Sassanid are coming.
This way.
[cacophony]
We'll head north
to the oasis at Ze Qar.
There. with the mountain
at our back.
we stand a chance.
[Samir] Kisra calls
for Hind's head.
Let him have it.
Perhaps then our actions
will be forgotten.
[battle drum music starts]
[Samir] What is it. my brother?
[soft music playing]
[creaks]
[wind howling]
[wind raging]
[horse grunts]
[horse neighs]
-[horse grunts]
-[wind howling]
[weird sounds]
[soft music playing]
[Hind] My father's dagger.
It's yours.
[bandit] Then
that leaves the gold.
[clings and cracks]
Does your father know
you're here?
My father is dead.
I'm going home.
To Al Hira?
Are you in a rush
to meet your father's fate?
My father sacrificed himself
for me.
Now I'm ready
to sacrifice myself
for my people.
Home is not always the way
you left it.
We need you to guide us.
Against an empire.
And I am the most wanted woman
in all of Arabia.
And no one.
except the shepherd boy.
will help me.
My brothers and I
made the journey
to Al Hira many times.
Then the Sassanid came.
That's how you got the scar?
From the one
they call Jalabzeen.
It's the same as the boy's.
You will ride faster alone.
We will ride further together.
I will take you.
[soft music playing]
But...
When we get there.
it is 60 pieces of gold.
[weird sounds]
[ominous music playing]
[thuds and echoes]
[stone hammering]
[battle drum music playing]
[birds swarming]
[battle drum music accelerates]
-[Safiya grunts]
-[Taif] Stop!
So. the prodigal one returns.
Those fire worshipers.
finally they tired
of your riddles?
Taif Bin Ganim.
Mother.
-I'm pleased to see my--
-Why are you here?
I bring news.
Hani of the Shaybani
has moved his people
to the oasis of Ze Qar.
Like you abandoned
your own tribe.
You threw me out.
You have no shame.
You dishonor the tribe.
By speaking my mind?
Ganim sentence for dishonor
without shame is death!
Then kill me!
[Safiya] Kill me
if that satisfies you.
[soft music playing]
But first. let me tell you
about true honor.
It isn't a weapon.
[slow music playing]
[Safiya] It's a journey.
[slow tempo music playing]
[fighting sounds]
[bandit] Come on.
[slow tempo music accelerates]
[both grunt]
[soft music playing]
Al Hira.
[dramatic music playing]
Are you sure
you want to do this?
[ominous music playing]
[cacophony]
[indistinct talking]
[dogs barking]
[Hind] Hey!
Is that Lakhmid gold you wear?
[crowd mumbling]
I am Hind Bint Al-Numan.
Queen of Al Hira.
[crowd mumbling]
I'm here to reclaim
my father's throne.
[giggles]
I see no throne.
[crowd mumbling]
[Kardarigan] Nor any loyal
to you.
Any last words
before I deliver your head?
[crowd gasp]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crowd mumbling]
[man shouting]
[crowd] Bastard. Leave us alone.
[crowd shouting]
[bandit grunts]
[slow tempo music playing]
Freedom!
[crowd in unison] Yeah!
[crowd cheering]
[crowd shouting]
[door knocking]
That is honor.
[slow tempo music accelerates]
[door knocking]
[crowd cheering]
[dog barking]
[somber music playing]
[tingling]
[crowd talking]
[Hind] Now you can rest
in the grove. Papa.
[thuds]
[soft music playing]
[hoofbeats]
[Hina] You've taken Al Hira?
They've destroyed everything.
I move my people to Ze Qar
where there is water.
It doesn't matter.
Kisra's army
will be unstoppable.
We'll fight together.
No.
You have your people.
Chief Hani.
I have mine.
Then I'll fight by your side.
as my queen.
[slow music playing]
[Hani] You are not alone.
You. too. have an army.
[tribal chant music playing]
[tribal music continues]
[rustling]
You came.
I'm not alone.
[Taif] Is what Safiya
tells true?
Did Kisra kill the Lakhmid king
and defile his body?
He dragged him through
the streets of Ctesiphon
with a camel's cowl.
Then he's no emperor.
[indistinct talking]
For once. my niece.
she speaks the truth.
[Taif] You have shown
yourself a queen.
-[knocks]
-[war chanting]
The Ganim will side with you.
For now.
-[men cheer] Kanifa!
-[man 9] Look. up there!
-[woman 3] How many?
-[man 9] Someone is coming!
[man 9] Where are they
coming from?
[crowd talking]
-[man 10] Kanifa!
-[men cheer] Kanifa!
[Hani] Let them pass.
[indistinct talking]
[footsteps]
[Eben] Chief Hani.
Eben Wael.
Taif Bin Ganim.
standing together? What next?
Will the sky drop snow?
To the empire.
we are all the same.
Yes. those Sassanid snakes
could never tell the difference
between us camels.
[Hind] Eben Wael.
I believe the last time
I saw you.
the Kanifa refused me
and my father a roof.
Hind Bint Al-Numan.
Queen of Al Hira.
[crowd mumbling]
Ah. the emperor's prize.
I can accept her being with us.
I... will lead us all
into battle.
[Hind] We welcome you
and the Kanifa.
but not your leadership.
-My ears must be dirty.
-[crowd gasp]
Do you understand
what you're saying. child?
Yes. Advice
and counsel. naturally.
This girl. Chief Hani?
I have refused an emperor.
Must I also refuse you?
[scoffs]
[Hind] You cast us out.
Eben Wael.
Or did you forget?
[crowd mumbling]
You have the desert
in front of you.
and the ocean behind.
You're trapped.
There is no escape
from what you will face.
[Eben] To win the battle.
you need an army.
[crowd mumbling]
I don't see an army here.
To win this battle.
you need tactics.
[Eben] Good position.
Well supplied. With water.
The oasis.
The oasis at Ze Qar
is where we will face them.
-An oasis.
-[man 11] Ze Qar.
-[man 12] Ze Qar.
-[children] Ze Qar!
-Ze Qar.
[crowd in unison] Ze Qar.
Ze Qar.
Ze Qar. Ze Qar.
Ze Qar! Ze Qar!
Well played. Queen of Al Hira.
Thank you. Eben Wael...
for your counsel.
[slow tempo music playing]
[men cheering]
[Taif] Ganim!
[men cheer] Ganim!
[marching footsteps]
Lakhmid!
[men cheer] Lakhmid!
[marching footsteps]
Shaybani!
-[men cheer] Shaybani!
-Shaybani!
[Eben] Kanifa!
[men cheer] Kanifa!
[battle drum music playing]
[wind rustling]
[wailing cry]
[men screaming]
[slow music playing]
[lumbering thumps]
[rustling]
My father would have wanted you
to have that.
[Hind] You earned it.
I've more than earned it.
You told me
we shared a common enemy.
I told you. honor is for fools.
[Hind] Kisra is coming.
[crowd singing]
So. where do you go
with your money?
Home?
No.
[bandit] Nowhere is home.
Take care of yourself. bandit.
[soft music playing]
[camel grunts]
Shh! Shh!
[slow tempo music playing]
[man 13 echoes]
Sassanid are coming!
[soft music playing]
[fighting and shouting sounds
in background]
-[horses neigh]
-[children's voice]
-[Jalabzeen] Are they dead?
-[men screaming]
[bandit] Look at me.
To be a man.
you must be brave and strong.
Can you be this man?
Brand this one.
[high-pitched dive sound]
[battle drum music playing]
[soft music playing]
Ze Qar!
[crowd cheering]
[slow tempo music playing]
Weapons!
[crowd] Weapons!
Aasif. we have to wait
for Hani's command.
[Samir] Aasif. we must wait.
Don't follow Aasif. please.
[Aasif] You have no right
to drink this water.
This is Shaybani land.
[men fighting sounds]
[Samir] Stop! Hani!
Go back. Back. Back!
Stop!
[indistinct shouting]
[Samir] Aasif!
You have no right
to drink this water.
[Aasif] This oasis
belongs to Shaybani.
I take it. you explain
who these outsiders are.
brother.
They're our allies. brother.
Kanifa. Lakhmid. Ganim.
They're here to fight with us.
Then they come to die.
Drink the water of Ze Qar.
Here.
-No. Stop them.
-Now.
Together.
[crowd cheering]
[soft music playing]
You've abandoned our people.
[Aasif] And our family.
Save your strength. Aasif.
You will need it.
May God protect us from you.
Brother.
I need you beside me
when we fight.
Not against me.
[dramatic music playing]
Come on.
[chordophone bowing]
Samir?
[sniffs and gasps]
Someone tried to poison me.
[man 14] Watch out!
[indistinct shouting]
[man 15] Aasif!
Aasif is leaving.
[man 14] You traitors!
Let's go!
-[man 15] Wake up!
-[man 14] Let's go!
Move out quickly!
[Hind] With him
goes our right flank.
[man 14] Let's go! Hyah!
[hoofbeats]
[Hani] He will tell them
how much water we are defending.
[buzzing]
[Hind] There are many ways
to fight this battle.
[Aasif] Ride fast!
We surrender to the Sassanid!
They will spare our lives!
[slow tempo music playing]
[plugging sounds]
[slow tempo music accelerates]
[water trickling]
[indistinct talking]
[water splashing]
[mysterious music playing]
[Qabisah] Commander Jalabzeen!
You have no idea
what it is like back there.
[hoofbeats]
[Qabisah] I can barely breathe.
[inaudible]
There's no water.
No water here.
Water!
[suspenseful music playing]
What is that desert rat doing?
[tribal music playing]
[Yazid yells] Bandit!
-[hoofbeats]
-[men cheering]
-[crowd talking]
-[camel groans]
[bandit grunts]
I come in peace.
[pants]
You brought the Tazmuri?
[bandit] Yeah. Yeah.
I know they are not
your favorite neighbors.
but they are good fighters.
-They've agreed
to fight with us?
-[bandit] Mm.
I told them
the army that is coming
is a caravan they could plunder.
Seemed like the best way
to get them here.
[chuckles]
-[Hani] It is quite the caravan.
-[Yazid] Where is he?
Where is that lying. cheating.
brigand. bandit. sour face?
Where is my caravan. Hani?
Greetings. Yazid.
He said it was
the largest caravan
he'd ever seen.
I said "colossal."
[Yazid] Colossal.
It's an army. Kisra's army.
I've joined a war on Kisra.
You used me.
How about I go
and see what Kisra will pay
for your heads?
Hind Bint Al-Numan.
Queen of the Lakhmid.
-The queen?
-Yazid of the Tazmuri.
We are grateful
for your allegiance.
and your men.
For...
[scoffs]
It was nothing.
[exhales]
It's an honor to meet you.
Hind Bint Al-Numan.
Why always yelling.
filthy thief?
That fig picker
is in on this too?
[grunting]
Get back. Go back.
[Taif] Having fun?
Since when does the Tazmuri
do anything
unless there's gold involved?
-Who else is in on this?
-We are many.
I have seen the army up close.
On the other side
of those hills.
My advice...
run while you can.
And where should we go?
I'll tell you where you've gone.
Wrong in the head.
How do you beat an empire?
-We let the desert beat it.
-Huh?
We've buried all the wells
beyond this oasis.
This is now the only water.
so we defend it.
You see? Instead of barking.
you should listen. Tactics.
This is how you beat Kisra.
[growls]
If the Tazmuri
will accept the honor.
you and your men could face off
on the right flank
against Ibn Qabisah
and his cavalry.
Ibn Qabisah?
-[spitting]
-[Hind] Yes.
I'd like to stick a lance
up that fat slob's--
Come on. come on. come on.
Join us for some food
and date wine.
-[Yazid] Date wine?
-[Hani] Yes. Three days old.
[Yazid] Three days?
[indistinct talking
and laughing]
[bandit] This belongs to you.
[men singing]
[men singing and dancing]
[shouting]
[tribal chanting]
[singing]
[slow music playing]
[Hani] Together...
we drink for tomorrow.
For Al-Numan's honor.
[Taif] Honor.
[men] Honor.
[sizzling]
-[chordophone bowing]
-[crowd mumbling]
[splashing]
[mysterious music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[crowd chattering]
[swishing]
[mysterious music plays]
[crowd shouting]
[man 16] Take them down!
For Kanifa!
[men cheering]
Ho! Ho! Ho!
[battle drum music playing]
[Taif yells] [inaudible]
[inaudible]
-[whistling]
-[children's voice]
[water trickling]
[battle drum music accelerates]
Keep digging!
[kid yells] [inaudible]
[Taif] Weapons.
Weapons.
Hey.
[indistinct talking]
[suspenseful music playing]
Shaybani will take the left!
Kanifa. the center!
Lakhmid with Hind!
Ganim will hold in reserve!
Use your own judgment
where and when to move!
[tribal battle music playing]
[hushing]
[high-pitched dive sound]
[rustling]
[rumbling]
[indistinct talking]
Settle!
Stay low.
[rumbling]
[hushing]
[tingling]
[horn sounding]
[man yells order]
-[horn sounding]
-[hoofbeats]
[battle drum music playing]
[horses neigh]
[Jalabzeen] How many tribes
have joined?
[men cheer] Kanifa.
[Al-Hamerz] Kanifa.
-And Lakhmid.
-[men cheering]
[tribal chanting]
Where is our Lakhmid heel?
Perhaps we should give the men
more water.
[Qabisah clears throat]
We are running low.
There are five thousand men
when 500 would suffice.
I have my orders.
Mhm.
[Qabisah grunts]
Time for your half-measures
is over.
Commander Jalabzeen.
We will water at Ze Qar
before the sun
is at its highest.
After I have destroyed
the Shaybani
and all the traitors
of my own tribe.
that have chosen
to die with them.
[Qabisah] Ganim? Kanifa?
What allegiance
do they have with each other?
Perhaps you should ask them.
Hm?
[horse neighs]
[Hind echoes] Ibn Qabisah!
You are no king!
I am your queen.
I will forgive you
and all other Lakhmids
if you ride to us
and fight
alongside your true people.
Look around you.
You are outnumbered four to one!
[Qabisah] You have raided.
robbed and cursed each other
for generations.
And yet. today.
you ride together as one?
Do not be fooled.
There's nothing that unites you.
[horses grunt]
[battle drum music playing]
[horse grunts]
You have placed yourself
and those who stand with you
in direct defiance
of His Majesty.
the Supreme Emperor...
-[arrow throwing]
-[thud]
-[horse neighs]
-[crowd cheering]
[indistinct talking]
[battle drum music playing]
[crunchy sounds]
Send Qabisah's Lakhmids
in first.
This will be swift.
[tingling]
[man yells order]
-[hoofbeats]
-[crowd chattering]
[man yells order]
And when they counter.
return them.
[hoofbeats]
[signaling]
[all signaling]
[boom]
[crowd shouting]
[tense music playing]
Is that a cow?
[rumbling]
[cows growling]
[growling]
-[grunting and screaming]
-[thudding]
[screaming]
[cows growling]
[men grunting and screaming]
[ominous music playing]
[man yells order]
[marching footsteps]
Tribes of Arabia.
[men cheering]
Are you with me?
[battle drum music playing]
[men shouting]
[Hani] For the fight!
[arrows shooting]
[Eben] Let the lions
tear down their house.
[battle drum music playing]
[thudding]
-[fighting sounds]
-[horses neigh]
[all grunting]
[fighting sounds continue
and people grunting]
Fight!
Outflank. Outflank.
[tingling]
[fighting sounds]
Keep them
from getting wide of us.
[fighting sounds continue]
[tense music playing]
[men war chanting and shouting]
[fighting sounds]
[shouting]
[men shouting]
-[shouting]
-[men shouting]
-[cracks]
-[indistinct shouting]
Signal both flanks.
Cavalry attacks on both wings.
[Jalabzeen]
Bracers center advance.
[battle drum music playing]
[running footsteps]
-[fighting sounds]
-[arrows shooting]
Wait. Wait.
Take the shield
to protect the line.
Take the shields
-[grunts]
-[indistinct shouting]
[man 17] Hold the line.
[suspenseful music playing]
They're going to break through.
[fighting sounds]
They're breaking the line.
There's a lot of them.
[yells] Keep them
behind that line!
[grunting]
Call the Ganim.
-[signaling]
-[men signaling]
Let's go!
[Taif] Let's show Kisra
what is it like to face a Ganim
who carries no sword
on his back.
Let's go.
[men cheering]
[Taif] Let's go!
[battle drum music playing]
[fighting sounds]
Hold them.
[men screaming]
Archers.
[Jalabzeen] Loose.
-[men shouting]
-[arrows shooting]
Bracers turn.
[fighting sounds]
[yelling]
[bandit] Go.
-Go. Go.
-[Hani grunts]
-[Hani] Go.
-[inaudible]
-[Hani] Go!
-[bandit] Retreat.
-Go.
-[Hani] Retreat.
[bandit] Retreat!
[Jalabzeen] No. no.
Cut them off.
Cut them off!
-[Hind grunts]
-[crowd shouting]
[Hani] Retreat!
Retreat!
Retreat! [grunts]
[Taif] Get back!
[Yazid] Get back.
[crowd shouting]
[Jalabzeen] Onward. Onward.
[panting]
[fighting sounds]
[crowd mumbling]
[indistinct shouting]
[arrows shooting]
[Hani grunts] Ah.
-[Jalabzeen] Make a line!
-[man 18] Make a line!
Make a line!
-Make a line.
-[Hind] Hold your fire.
[soft music playing]
[man 18] Hold the line!
[Hani groans]
-[Jalabzeen] Give us the girl.
-[Hani] No.
No.
[somber music playing]
[pants]
[Hani] Hind.
It's my sacrifice.
Give me the girl!
[Hani pants]
-[swish]
-[crowd gasp]
[Samir] No! Hani!
-[Jalabzeen] Withdraw.
-[man 18] Bracers!
Withdraw!
[Jalabzeen] Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
[man 18] Turn!
Let me go.
[Samir yelling]
[hoofbeats]
[Samir] Hani.
Hani.
[Jalabzeen] Crush them
into dust.
[horn sounding]
[man shouting]
[crowd chattering]
We face them with camels.
Camels!
[Taif] The camels! The camels!
[screams]
[rumbling]
[men shouting]
[camel grunts]
[Taif] Go! Let's go! Let's move!
[man 19] Let's move.
[battle drum music playing]
[men screaming]
-[lumbering thumps]
-[camels groan]
-[rumbling]
-[elephant roaring]
Hold the lines!
[man 20] Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
[elephants roaring]
[driver] Thirty!
[men shouting]
Cover the camels' eyes!
Blindfold them!
Twenty!
Ten!
Five!
Brace!
[man 21] Release!
-[arrows shooting]
-[elephant roaring]
[collapsing sounds]
-[Taif grunts]
-[elephant roaring]
[indistinct shouting]
-[rumbling]
-[elephants roaring]
[bandit] Pull back!
There are too many!
[pants]
[elephant trumpets]
-[elephant trumpets]
-[rustling]
Retreat! Retreat! Retreat!
Go. To the oasis!
[Jalabzeen] Finish this!
[Al-Hamerz] Full advance!
[indistinct shouting]
[ominous music playing]
We need some water!
Seize the oasis!
[men shouting]
-[man 22] Run! Move!
-[man 23] Out quickly. go!
[man 24] Run!
-[grunts]
-[indistinct shouting]
-[Safiya] We have to leave!
-[man 25] Hide! Hide!
-[man 22] Go!
-[man 23] Go. go. go!
[mysterious music playing]
[men cheering]
[whistling]
[water splashing]
[men shouting]
[men cheering]
[ominous music playing]
[pants]
[vomiting and coughing]
[screams] Stop!
Stop drinking!
[hush falling over]
The water is poisoned!
-[arrow shooting]
-[grunts and gasps for air]
[soft muffled music playing]
[pants]
[muffled sounds]
[muffled music playing]
[thump]
[fighting sounds]
[grunting]
[panting and grunting]
[hush falling over]
[slow music playing]
[panting]
[Hind grunts]
[grunts and pants]
[pants]
[wind rustling]
[Jalabzeen] Home.
[thud]
[soft music playing]
[tribal chanting]
[crowd cheering]
[horse grunts]
He chose you.
He is free to do so.
And you?
[classical music playing]
I hope to see you again.
Hind Bint Al-Numan of Al Hira.
You should be so blessed.
Hyah!
-[crowd cheering and singing]
-Hyah!
[soft music playing]
[tribal music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[crowd cheering and singing]
[victory music playing]
[tribal music playing]
[soft music playing]
♪ Seeds are falling
Like heavy gold ♪
♪ Keeps us human
From getting old ♪
♪ Treasure nature ♪
♪ With every turn
You go ♪
♪ Always here ♪
♪ Seeds are falling
Like heavy gold ♪
♪ Keeps us human
From getting old ♪
♪ Treasure nature ♪
♪ With every turn
You go ♪
♪ Always here ♪
♪ Seeds are falling
Like heavy gold ♪
♪ Keeps us human
From getting old ♪
♪ Treasure nature ♪
♪ With every turn
You go ♪
♪ Always here ♪
[orchestral music playing]
[slow music playing]
[music ends]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm